

## **JORGE SARRICOLEA**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

LinkedInd Mérida, Yucatán +52 938 109 5593

ABOUT M	1 E	
ABOUT M		

I am a Web Developer specialized in UI/UX Design, with 2 years of experience working on different projects. I am a Personal Finance and Technology enthusiast, always keeping up with the latest trends, and have the ability to learn anything I set my mind to.

Check my own page: jorgesarricolea.com

WORK EXPERIENCE \_\_\_\_\_\_

Weather APP | March 2023 - April 2023

GitHub: Weather-APP

I used the free OpenWeatherMap API with a minimalist and responsive design, and I work with the icons that this API contains. It shows an error message and ask the user to try again if they enter an invalid value.

The Movies APP | June 2023 - July 2023

Link: the-movies-app

Developed with NextJS, TypeScript, and TailwindCSS. I used TheMovieDB API to fetch all the data displayed on the frontend of this project. This project was deployed with Vercel.

Web Developer | Datamatic Software | June 2022 - July 2022

LinkedIn: Datamatic Software

I worked on different projects, designing the user interface from scratch, adding new features, and utilizing backend workflows and reusable components for various projects.

Full Stack Developer | Jumwork | January 2018 - January 2022

Link: jumwork.com

I designed the whole brand, user experience and user interface from scratch on Bubble. Integration with Stripe API and others in backend process. Worked with differents plugins, like Sendgrid and upgraded old pages to the new responsive engine.

EDUCATION \_\_\_\_\_

Computer System Engineering | August 2020 – Present

Instituto Tecnológico de Mérida

Platzi Certificates

Frontend Developer Course | 2022 HTML and CSS Practical Course | 2021 Software Engineering Fundamentals | 2021 Interface Design Course | 2020

SKILLS \_\_\_\_\_\_

Programming, frameworks and cloud

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, React, Boostrap, TailwindCSS, Jest, NodeJS, NextJS, Python, AWS

Tools and design enverioment

Git Version Control, VSCode, Trello, Notion, Miro, Figma, Abobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop

**Others** 

Conversational English, quick and continuous learning, adaptability, problem solving capacity, teamwork, leadership, communicative, creative, responsible, honest